http://www.latos.org/terms-privacy/

Agreement between user and latos.org
Welcome to latos.org. The latos.org website (the “Site”) is comprised of various web pages operated by LATOS latos.org is offered to you conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and notices contained herein (the “Terms”). Your use of latos.org constitutes your agreement to all such Terms. Please read these terms carefully, and keep a copy of them for your reference.
latos.org is a Non-profit Site
The purpose of the LATOS website is to provide organizational information and news.
Privacy
Your use of latos.org is subject to LATOS’s Privacy Policy. Please review our Privacy Policy, which also governs the Site and informs users of our data collection practices.
Electronic Communications
Visiting latos.org or sending emails to LATOS constitutes electronic communications. You consent to receive electronic communications and you agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically, via email and on the Site, satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.
LATOS does not knowingly collect, either online or offline, personal information from persons under the age of thirteen. If you are under 18, you may use latos.org only with permission of a parent or guardian.
Links to third party sites/Third party services
latos.org may contain links to other websites (“Linked Sites”). The Linked Sites are not under the control of LATOS and LATOS is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. LATOS is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by LATOS of the site or any association with its operators.
Certain services made available via latos.org are delivered by third party sites and organizations. By using any product, service or functionality originating from the latos.org domain, you hereby acknowledge and consent that LATOS may share such information and data with any third party with whom LATOS has a contractual relationship to provide the requested product, service or functionality on behalf of latos.org users and customers.
No unlawful or prohibited use/Intellectual Property
You are granted a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to access and use latos.org strictly in accordance with these terms of use. As a condition of your use of the Site, you warrant to LATOS that you will not use the Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms. You may not use the Site in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Site or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Site. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the Site.
All content included as part of the Service, such as text, graphics, logos, images, as well as the compilation thereof, and any software used on the Site, is the property of LATOS or its suppliers and protected by copyright and other laws that protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe and abide by all copyright and other proprietary notices, legends or other restrictions contained in any such content and will not make any changes thereto.
You will not modify, publish, transmit, reverse engineer, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any of the content, in whole or in part, found on the Site. LATOS content is not for resale. Your use of the Site does not entitle you to make any unauthorized use of any protected content, and in particular you will not delete or alter any proprietary rights or attribution notices in any content. You will use protected content solely for your personal use, and will make no other use of the content without the express written permission of LATOS and the copyright owner. You agree that you do not acquire any ownership rights in any protected content. We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the intellectual property of LATOS or our licensors except as expressly authorized by these Terms.
Third Party Accounts
You will be able to connect your LATOS account to third party accounts. By connecting your LATOS account to your third party account, you acknowledge and agree that you are consenting to the continuous release of information about you to others (in accordance with your privacy settings on those third party sites). If you do not want information about you to be shared in this manner, do not use this feature.
International Users
The Service is controlled, operated and administered by LATOS from our offices within the USA. If you access the Service from a location outside the USA, you are responsible for compliance with all local laws. You agree that you will not use the LATOS Content accessed through latos.org in any country or in any manner prohibited by any applicable laws, restrictions or regulations.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless LATOS, its officers, directors, employees, agents and third parties, for any losses, costs, liabilities and expenses (including reasonable attorneys’ fees) relating to or arising out of your use of or inability to use the Site or services, any user postings made by you, your violation of any terms of this Agreement or your violation of any rights of a third party, or your violation of any applicable laws, rules or regulations. LATOS reserves the right, at its own cost, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you, in which event you will fully cooperate with LATOS in asserting any available defenses.
Liability disclaimer
THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. LATOS AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME.
LATOS AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. LATOS AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL LATOS AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SITE, WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF LATOS OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THE SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE.
Termination/access restriction
LATOS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the Site and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by the laws of the State of California and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in California in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of the Site. Use of the Site is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms, including, without limitation, this section.
You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and LATOS as a result of this agreement or use of the Site. LATOS’s performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of LATOS’s right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of the Site or information provided to or gathered by LATOS with respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall continue in effect.
Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the user and LATOS with respect to the Site and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and LATOS with respect to the Site. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent an d subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be written in English.
Changes to Terms
LATOS reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Terms under which latos.org is offered. The most current version of the Terms will supersede all previous versions. LATOS encourages you to periodically review the Terms to stay informed of our updates.
Contact Us
LATOS welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Terms:
Telephone number:
(888) 528-6722
Effective as of September 04, 2013
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the latos.org and LATOS and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to LATOS include latos.org. The LATOS website is a non-profit site. By using the LATOS website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
LATOS may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. LATOS may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age and gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by LATOS. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the LATOS website.
LATOS encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from LATOS so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. LATOS is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the LATOS website.
Use of your Personal Information
LATOS collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
LATOS may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from LATOS and its affiliates. LATOS may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
LATOS does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
LATOS may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to LATOS, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
LATOS may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within LATOS, in order to determine what LATOS services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within LATOS to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
LATOS will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LATOS or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of LATOS; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of LATOS, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The LATOS website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize LATOS pages, or register with LATOS site or services, a cookie helps LATOS to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same LATOS website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the LATOS features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the LATOS services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
LATOS secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Children Under Thirteen
LATOS does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from LATOS by contacting us here:
– Phone: (888) 528-6722
Changes to this Statement
LATOS will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. LATOS encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how LATOS is protecting your information.
Contact Information
LATOS welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that LATOS has not adhered to this Statement, please contact LATOS at:
Telephone number:
(888) 528-6722
Effective as of September 04, 2013
Sign Up
Stay posted on upcoming events and more!
Home
Contact
Terms & Privacy
© 2020 Los Angeles Theatre Organ Society. All rights reserved.
Website by Mark Herman Design.
